<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Custom Blog - Home to All Things People Oriented]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Custom Blog - Home to All Things People Oriented]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 14:53:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selin Kumbarci ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Selin Kumbarci </h1><p> Coming far away from the capital of Turkey, Selin is probably one of the most energetic and loudest people on campus. Known for her love of current events, history and Model United Nations, Selin is very much in- terested in international relations and affairs. Ever since the 6th grade, Selin has been participating in Model Unit- ed Nations. To be honest, she joined because a freshman in her school told her it would help her with her college applications. In the beginning, she was an admin and she instantly enjoyed the feeling of watching a conference. So, she did not only settle for admin, but became a delegate. She has always liked the idea of dressing up, being formal, and the fancy atmosphere one feels during conferences. Aside from Model United Nations, Selin has been actively partic- ipating in writing articles for newspapers, whether school or outside of school. What you may not know is that not only does she write for Catalysm, she also writes for an online newspaper called the United Youth Journalists. This is a newspaper which is creat- ed by students from all around the world to de- liver perspectives of the youth on issues from all around the world. Selin has always had an interest in the media in general. In regards to her passion, Selin has multiple interests. Everything from edu- cation to neuropsychology. When she was younger, she actually wanted to be a teacher for a short period of time. However, she is still continu- ing to search for what exactly she wants to do in her life. </p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/502093b4f7a6680f1264661b6eb3a402/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=5472&cropwidth=3649&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F56110287-1426-475f-bfda-53fbc9f9099d.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/selin-kumbarci/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">96a354f6-eca9-4a53-808d-63eb2f6539ef</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 14:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rex Kingston]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rex Kingston</h1><p>His past filled with ups and downs galore, Rex views himself as your average kid, though eaning slightly towards the negative side. For instance, he sees himself as a “spoiled brat” who</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/36f47f8b1b267c27d2871ff3d9e62319/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=5472&cropwidth=3649&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Ff3f48491-b71c-4d46-b721-42fed02ae79e.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/rex-kingston/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee5a6484-0575-4115-907a-232ef1cd8098</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 10:12:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Haruka Tone]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Haruka Tone</h1><p>Many people may perceive Haruka as a quiet girl, do not let this blind you. Haruka actually describes herself as a person who loves to break the status quo, break the rules, and be loud. She loves to explore the world and make nature her own.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/haruka-tone/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">75ec9ba2-4bc0-4455-810d-76280981a549</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 10:07:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE PARADOX OF LOVE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>THE PARADOX OF LOVE</h1><p>Written by Abha Awasthi</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/the-paradox-of-love/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1c9c96dc-0814-42d4-a0fe-a46dc885d295</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 10:03:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boom Tongsamui]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Boom Tongsamui</h1><p>Probably known as the clown of the Class of 2017, Boom has always enjoyed making people laugh, being cheerful and silly, but also doing embarrassing things. Boom believes if you do not believe something is embarrassing, you can have the time of your life.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/custom-blog/boom-tongsamui/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7e62bcf0-78c3-48ee-b2c7-55071099fc5f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 09:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>